<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder
	xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">
	<ui:style>
		.centerContent {
			height: 100%;
			max-height: 650px;
			border: 1px #ff7f00 solid;
			border-radius: 4px;
			overflow-y: auto;
			background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.7);
		}
		
		.welcome {
			padding: 15px;
			max-width: 500px;
			margin-left: auto;
			margin-right: auto;
		}
		
		.welcome h1 {
			margin-top: .5em;
			margin-bottom: .5em;
			font-size: large;
			color: #ff7f00;
		}
		
		.welcome h2 {
			margin-top: .5em;
			margin-bottom: .25em;
			color: #ff7f00;
		}
		
		.welcome hr {
			margin: 1em 0;
		}
		
		.welcome ul {
			list-style-type: disc;
		}
		
		.welcome p,li {
			margin-bottom: .75em;
		}
	</ui:style>
	<g:HTML styleName="{style.centerContent}">
		<div class="{style.welcome}">
			<h1>Welcome to CommonSense</h1>
			<p>
				Your smartphone may be called a “smart” phone, but we at Sense still think that your phone is
				very stupid. Your phone is packed full of sensors, but still
				<i>knows</i>
				very little about you.
			</p>
			<p>CommonSense is meant to change that.</p>
			<p>The Sense Platform app is gathering sensor data from your smartphone. Here, in CommonSense,
				you can access this data. Just log in with your Sense account, and drag the sensors you like to
				view into this main panel. For further explanation, read the Tutorials.</p>
			<hr />
			<h2>Possible applications</h2>
			<p> All this might just seem like a funny gimmick, but we plan to incorporate some intelligent
				and helpful features into CommonSense, by having the system get to know you and your network.
				Just some examples: 
			</p>
			<ul>
				<li>Why does your phone even bother to ring, when it can sense that you are driving at 120
					kilometers per hour on a motorway? What if it would automatically send out a text message,
					telling people you will call back when you have arrived at your destination? 
				</li>
				<li>You may think you will never see that guy you met on holiday again. What if your smartphones
					would give you both a heads up when you are in the same city? 
				</li>
				<li>Sometimes it is very practical that your phone reminds you of an appointment. But what is
					the use of a reminder to go to the dentist when you are already sitting in the waiting room?
					Your phone knows where you are, and if it would only use the calendar function, it could know
					where you have to be. It would only have to warn you if you are going to be late. 
				</li>
				<li>And why do we have to keep telling social media like Facebook and Twitter where we are, when
					our phone knows already?</li>
			</ul>
		</div>
	</g:HTML>
</ui:UiBinder>